

# CONTACT

609-638-0624

## **PROFILE**

Detailed oriented administrative assistant, experienced with day to day operational and logistical needs of the front-line, including: booking appointments, maintaining daily operations, identify management and staff needs, communicate directly with management, staff and clients, and performs basic tasks as needed and authorized.

#### SKILLS

- MICROSOFT OFFICE
- **MULTI-TASKING**
- TIME MANAGEMENT
- ATTENTION TO DETAIL AND **FOLLOW-THROUGH**
- **CLIENT RELATIONS SPECIALIST**
- **QUICKBOOKS**

#### **EDUCATION**

**Brookdale Community** College

2012

**Business Administration** 

**Asbury Park High School** 2008

### EXPERIENCE

## **Administrative Assistant**

TownePlace Suites Hotel

2018-2019

Provide administrative support to the hotel General Manager and front desk team. Answer telephones and emails related to booking hotel stays. Maintain calendars, coordinating extensive appointments, meetings and travel accommodations. Maintain the profit and loss statements to ensure that hotel maintains the yearly budget.

# **Account Payable Specialist**

Monmouth Telecom

2016-2018

Responsibilities involve providing financial, administrative and clerical support to the organization. Completing payments and control expenses by receiving payments, plus processing, verifying and reconciling invoices.

#### Senior Teller

PNC Bank

2013-2016

Responsibilities included: Manage cash controls and to maintain accurate level for ATM responsibilities for processing shipment

High School Diploma

protocols. Being able to engage and meet the client's financial well-being; operations of the client experience; Exceeds expectations on year end reviews; participated in focus groups to enhance the teller experience; cross sell products to clients; assist operations manager in completing monthly and quarterly reports and gather information to meet the BSA guidelines.

# Affordable Housing Alliance

Administrative Assistant (Intern)

2011-2012

Handled the resident's questions, complaints, and concerns to take the necessary steps to resolve the situations. Prepared the weekly collection and variance / budget reports for the Director. Updated the weekly reports concerning notices to vacate, vacancy reports, activity reports, etc. Assisted the leasing staff, making sure all follow-ups were made to prospects to ensure occupancy goals were made.